{"data":[{"question":"Jim's counselor recommended that he should take a foreign language in his freshman year instead of waiting until the following year.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"he should take","b":"in his","c":"of waiting","d":"the","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n - He should take-> he take","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"Visitors are not permitted entering the park after dark because of the lack of security and lighting.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Visitors","b":"entering","c":"because of","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Entering-> to enter","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"Marcy said that she knew how the procedures for doing the Experiment, but when we began to work in the laboratory, she found that she was mistaken.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"knew how","b":"to work","c":"found that","d":"mistaken","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Knew how-> knew","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"Jack's professor had him to rewrite his thesis many times before allowing him to present it to the committee.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to rewrite","b":"many times","c":"allowing him","d":"to the committee","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- To rewrite-> rewrite","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"We wish today was Sunday so that we could spend the day in the country communing with nature.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"so that","c":"could spend","d":"in the","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Was-> were","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"Standing among so many strangers the frightened child began to sob uncontrollable.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Standing among","b":"the frightened","c":"to sob","d":"uncontrollable","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Uncontrollable-> uncontrollablely","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"Max's new sport car costs much more than his friend Joe.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"sport","b":"costs","c":"much more","d":"friend Joe","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Friend Joe-> friend's Joe\nHis friend's-> his friend's sport car","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"Paul did so well in his speech today that he should have rehearsed it many times the past week.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"so","b":"that","c":"should have","d":"the past week","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Should have-> should have had","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"Our Spanish professor would like us spending more time in the laboratory practicing our pronunciation.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"us","b":"spending","c":"time","d":"practicing","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Spending-> to spend","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"},{"question":"Sally must have called her sister last night, but she arrived home too late to call her.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"must have called","b":"arrived","c":"too late","d":"her","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Must have called-> had to call","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"35","type":"1"}]}